Ninety minutes. Six bullets. No choice.
Nick of Time is a thriller, crime, action film directed by John Badham.
An ordinary man is suddenly forced into a plot to kill a politician
in exchange for his kidnapped daughter's freedom.
Gene Watson, played by Johnny Depp.
Lynn Watson, played by Courtney Chase.
Hucy, played by Charles S. Dutton.
Mr. Smith, played by Christopher Walken.
Ms. Jones, played by Roma Maffia.
Brendan Grant, played by Peter Strauss.
Nick of Time is a 1995 American political action thriller film produced and
directed by John Badham and written by Patrick Sheane Duncan.
It stars Johnny Depp, Christopher Walken, Charles S.
Dutton, and Courtney Chase.
Taking place in real time, the film follows Gene Watson, a public accountant who must assassinate
politician Governor Eleanor Grant in exchange for his kidnapped daughter Lynn's freedom.
It was released theatrically in the United States by
Paramount Pictures on November 22, 1995.
The film explores themes of assassination, politics, los angeles, california.
The tone is intense.